escortsandbabes.com.au 2019-04-06

# Privacy Policy - Escorts and Babes

### Escorts and Babes Privacy Policy

Escorts and Babes.com Pty Ltd ABN 36 139 493 726 ( **Escorts and Babes** ), Queensland, Australia, recognises and values the protection of your personal information. This Privacy Policy forms part of the Website Terms of Use.

Your privacy is important to us. If you have any questions regarding our information practices and other privacy aspects of the Site, you can contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#6d0c090004032d081e0e021f191e0c03090f0c0f081e430e0200430c18521e180f07080e19503c18081f14485f5d1f080a0c1f0904030a485f5d1402181f485f5d3d1f041b0c0e14485f5d3d0201040e14).

The term **personal information** in this Privacy Policy means any information from which your identity is apparent or can be reasonably ascertained.

### **Consent**

You warrant that you are able to give consents under applicable law. You hereby expressly and voluntarily grant your informed consent to Escorts and Babes to deal with your personal information in accordance with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

You can retract your consent by contacting us at INSERT as soon as possible. If you retract your consent, you acknowledge and agree that failure to provide certain types of personal information may not give you access to the full functionality of the Site.

### **Information we collect from you**

From time to time, we may collect your contact information (such as your email address). You may also supply us with your personal information if you register for any paid services or if you use the contact form on the Site.

Occasionally, we may conduct surveys or market research and in doing so, we may seek other information from you. This will provide us with information that allows us to improve the type and quality of Site and any services offered to you, and the manner in which the Site and services are offered to you.

We may also request personal information from you in order to supply you with our paid services (for GST purposes).

### Cookies

We utilise cookies which enable us to monitor traffic patterns and to serve you more efficiently if you revisit the Site. A cookie does not identify you personally but it does identify your computer. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie and this will provide you with an opportunity to either accept or reject it in each instance.

###  **Use of your personal information**

Unless you object, your personal information may be used to: 

  * send news, information about our activities and general promotional material which we believe may be useful to you;
  * monitor who is accessing the Site or using services offered on the Site;
  * profile the type of people accessing the Site;
  * ensure the proper functioning of the Site; and
  * assist us with our marketing, planning, development and research requirements.

If you request us not to use personal information in a particular manner or at all, we will adopt all reasonable measures to observe your request but we may still use or disclose that information if we: 

  * subsequently notify you of the intended use or disclosure and you do not object to that use or disclosure;
  * believe that the use or disclosure is reasonably necessary to assist a law enforcement agency or an agency responsible for government or public scrutiny in the performance of their functions; or
  * are required by law to disclose the information.

### **Disclosure of your personal information**

We may disclose personal information to our service providers who assist us in operating the Site. We will only disclose personal information to a third party unrelated to Escorts and Babes with your consent.

Apart from such circumstances, we may disclose personal information in special situations where we have reason to believe that doing so is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against anyone damaging, injuring or interfering (intentionally or unintentionally) with our rights or property, users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.

We may also disclose personal information as required by law.

In the event that we sell or buy businesses or their assets, or engage in transfers, acquisitions, mergers, restructurings, changes of control and other similar transactions, customer information is generally one of the transferable business assets. Thus, your personal information may be subject to such a transfer. In the unlikely event of insolvency, personal information may be transferred to a trustee or debtor in possession and then to a subsequent purchaser.

If you voluntarily provide information in publicly accessible areas of the Site, the information can be viewed and therefore used by others. We advise users not to disclose contact information that they do not wish to have publicly available. We are not responsible for personal information you choose to submit publicly.

###  **Security**

You must do what you reasonably can to ensure the security of your personal information. It is your obligation that you protect yourself against unauthorised access to your password and to your computer. Please log out of the Site when you have finished using a shared computer. Be wary of including sensitive information in your emails to us as they are not necessarily secure against interception. We will not ask for passwords in an email and you should assume that if you get such a request, it must be fraudulent.

We have processes in place to ensure the security of your personal information. We have procedures to help safeguard and prevent unauthorised access, maintain data security, and correctly use your information. However, neither people nor security systems are infallible, including encryption systems. While we use reasonable efforts to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We have obligations under the _Privacy Act 1988 (Cth)_ to notify you if you are affected by an eligible data breach. We will take all reasonable precautions to take remedial action to prevent such an event. As we cannot guarantee that remedial action will be sufficient to prevent all instances of a breach, we will take steps to notify you of an eligible data breach as soon as practicable and provide recommendations as to what steps you should take to mitigate any serious loss or damage.

###  **Access and correction**

You are entitled access to, and correct, the personal information we hold about you in certain circumstances. If you would like to obtain such access, please contact us on the details set out above.

Please note that the access and correction requirements under this Privacy Policy operates alongside and do not replace other informal or legal procedures by which an individual can be provided access to, or correction of, their personal information, including the requirements under the _Freedom of Information Act 1982 (Cth)_.

###  **Complaint**

You may make a complaint to us about any alleged breaches of privacy. To do so, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#fa9b9e979394ba9f899995888e899b949e989b989f89d4999597d49b8fc5898f98909f998ec7ab8f9f8883dfc8ca889f9d9b889e93949ddfc8ca83958f88dfc8caaa88938c9b9983dfc8caaa9596939983), with the following information: 

  * your name and address;
  * details of the alleged breach of privacy; and
  * Uniform Resource Locator link to the alleged breach of privacy (if applicable).

Please allow us 30 days to investigate your complaint, after which we will contact you immediately to resolve the issue.

###  **Retention of Information**

We retain information for as long as required, allowed or we believe it useful, but do not undertake retention obligations. We may dispose of information in our discretion without notice, subject to applicable law that specifically requires the handling or retention of information. You must keep your own, separate back-up records.

###  **Transfer out of Australia**

The Site is currently hosted in Australia. However, we may choose to set up more servers in countries outside of Australia in the future and we may transfer data on the Site (including all personal information) to our hosting service providers and data centres located overseas. You hereby expressly and voluntarily grant your informed consent to such transfers.

###  **Updates to Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately. If we make a significant change to the Privacy Policy, we may issue a notice by email or through notice on the home page of the Site.

It is your sole responsibility to periodically check this Privacy Policy for any changes. If you do not agree to any changes in this Privacy Policy, you must immediately cease using the Site. Your continued use of the Site will be deemed as your acceptance of such changes.

Last updated: 05-06-18
